So I had a brother reach out to me
and let me know that he was going through foreclosure
and then he started to be attacked by on the road policy enforcers right
in the midst of that he was also uh
being put into court because his baby mom wanted to put him on child support
and that's just too much shit for me okay?
That's just too much going on for one person to deal with at all
at one time at that right?
So I told him what to do and I gave him step by step what
what to do and how to go about it
step one was for him to accept the deed of his life okay?
You have to claim that a minor account of the estate
you have to and then once you do that
the court so you have to notify these policy enforces that um
this estate is claimed baby
I am heir and beneficiary of this estate there is an occupant okay?
One thing y'all gotta understand
is that the government is not gonna chase around nobody
that they don't see value in
if there's no monetary value
they not gonna chase you around that what what they wanna chase you around for
but when they know that there's value on your name and you worth some money oh
it's gonna be hell in hot water
but you can bring it right back on down by claiming that account
Claiming that account and notify them.